Guide to the Graham Arthur Barden Papers, 1934-1960
Graham Arthur Barden papers 1934-1960
- Subject Series
  - B. Military
    - 1. Installations
      - Stallings Air Force Base, Kinston, N. C., 1957 (Folder 340)
      - Military Installations: Correspondence, A-F (Folder 341-342)
      - Military Installations: Correspondence, G-Z (Box 55, Folder 343-347)
    - 2. Universal training (Box 55)
      - Military Draft, 1948 (Folder 348)
      - Universal Military Training: Special, 1951 (Folder 349)
      - Universal Military Training: Special, 1951 (Box 56, Folder 350-352)
      - 18 Year Old Draft: General (Folder 353-355)
      - 18 Year Old Draft: General (Box 57, Folder 356-361)
      - 18 Year Old Draft: General (Box 58, Folder 362-364)
      - Universal Military Training (Black notebook) (Folder 365)
      - Universal Military Training: Special, 1952 (Folder 366-367)
      - Universal Military Training: Special, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 368-369)
      - Universal Military Training: General, 1952 (Folder 370-373)
      - Universal Military Training: General, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 374-379)
      - Universal Military Training: General, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 380-383)
      - Universal Military Training: 1953-1954 (Folder 384)
      - Universal Military Training: 1955(Floor debate) (Folder 385)
      - Universal Military Training: Special, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 386)
      - Universal Military Training: General, 1955 (Folder 387-391)
      - Universal Military Training: General, 1955 (Box 63, Folder 392-393)
      - Universal Military Training: 1956(Rreserve Forces Act) (Folder 394)
    - 3. Service Academies
      - Air Force Academy (Box 63, Folder 395)
      - Army: Miscellaneous (Folder 396)
      - West Point (Folder 397-398)
      - West Point (Box 64, Folder 399-400)
      - Coast Guard Academy (Folder 401)
      - Merchant Marine Academy (Folder 402)
      - Naval Academy (Folder 403-406)
      - Service Academy Applications, Caffrey-Clark (Folder 407)
      - Service Academy Applications, Clark-Cummings (Box 65, Folder 408-409)
    - 4. Veterans
      - Veterans, Caffrey-Carraway (Box 65, Folder 410-413)
      - Veterans, Carraway-Cotton (Box 66, Folder 414-419)
      - Veterans, Coward-Cuthrell (Box 67, Folder 420-423)
  - C. Employment
    - Employment, Cade-Cannon (Box 67, Folder 424-425)
    - Employment, Cannon-Cason (Box 68, Folder 426-431)
    - Employment, Cash-Cook (Box 69, Folder 432-437)
    - Employment, Cook-Croom (Box 70, Folder 438-444)
    - Employment, Croom-Cutler (Box 71, Folder 445)
  - D. Post Office
    - Post Office: Miscellaneous (Box 71, Folder 446)
    - Post Office Department (Folder 447)
    - Bayboro (Pamlico Co.) Post Office (Folder 448)
    - Burgaw (fender Co.) Post Office (Folder 449-451)
    - Clinton (Sampson Co.) Post Office (Folder 452-453)
    - Clinton Post Office (Box 72, Folder 454-458)
    - Goldsboro (Wayne Co.) Post Office (Folder 459-460)
    - Goldsboro Post Office (Box 73, Folder 461-463)
    - Jacksonville (Onslow Co.) Post Office (Folder 464-466)
    - Jacksonville Post Office (Box 74, Folder 467-468)
    - Kenansville (Duplin Co.) Post Office (Folder 469-470)
    - Morehead City (Folder 471-473)
    - New Bern (Craven Co.) Post Office (Box 75, Folder 474-480)
    - New Bern Post Office (Box 76, Folder 481-484)
    - Trenton (Jones Co.) Post Office (Folder 485-486)
- Series II--Education and Labor
  - 74th Congress 1935-1936
    - Education (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Library Committee (Folder 2)
    - Labor: Wagner Bill (Folder 3)
    - Labor: General
  - 75th Congress 1937-1938
    - Education (Box 77, Folder 5-7)
    - Labor (Folder 8-10)
    - Labor (Box 78, Folder 11-17)
  - 76th Congress 1939-1940
    - Education (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Labor (Folder 19-23)
    - Labor (Box 80, Folder 24-29)
    - Labor (Box 81, Folder 30-35)
    - Labor (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - 77th Congress 1941-1942
    - Education: General (Box 82, Folder 37)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation (Blind) (Folder 38)
    - Library Committee (Folder 39)
    - Labor (Folder 40-41)
  - 78th Congress 1943-1944
    - Education: General (Box 82, Folder 42)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation (Folder 43-44)
    - Advisory Commission on the Study of Higher Education (Folder 45)
    - Advisory Commission (continued) (Box 83, Folder 46)
    - Library (Folder 47)
    - Labor (Folder 48)
  - 79th Congress 1945-1946
    - Education: General (Box 83, Folder 49-50)
    - Education: Vocational (Box 83, Folder 51-53)
    - Education: Vocational (Box 84, Folder 54)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation (Folder 55)
    - Report of the Advisory Commission on the Study of Higher Education (Folder 56-57)
    - Library (Folder 58)
    - Labor (Folder 59-61)
  - 80th Congress 1947-1948
    - Education: Federal Aid (Box 85, Folder 62)
    - Vocational (Folder 63)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation (Folder 64)
    - Joint Committee on Labor-Management Relations: Taft-Hartley Act (Folder 65-69)
    - Joint Committee on Labor-Management Relations: Taft-Hartley Act (Box 86, Folder 70-72)
    - Labor (Folder 73)
  - 81st Congress 1949-1950
    - Education & Labor Comm.: General Papers (Folder 74)
    - Education--General: Burke Bill (Folder 75-77)
    - Education--General: Burke Bill (Box 87, Folder 78)
    - Education:
      - General (Folder 79)
      - Federal Aid (Comparative print) (Folder 80)
      - Federal Aid (Jan.-June 1949) (Folder 81-85)
      - Federal Aid (June 1949) (Box 88, Folder 86-91)
      - Federal Aid (June-July, 1949) (Box 89, Folder 92-97)
      - Federal Aid (July 1949) (Box 90, Folder 98-104)
      - Federal Aid (July 1949) (Box 91, Folder 105-111)
      - Federal Aid (July 1949) (Box 92, Folder 112-118)
      - Federal Aid (July 1949) (Box 93, Folder 119-124)
      - Federal Aid (Aug. 1949) (Box 94, Folder 125-130)
      - Federal Aid (Aug. 1949-early 1950) (Box 95, Folder 131-136)
      - Federal Aid (1950, Feb.-Apr.) (Box 96, Folder 137-142)
      - Federal Aid (1950, Apr.-Dec.) (Box 97, Folder 143-147)
      - Federal Aid, Miscellaneous (Box 148-149)
      - Federal Aid, Speeches (Box 98, Folder 150)
      - Federal Aid, Atlanta Speech (Folder 151)
      - Federal Aid, Printed Material (Folder 152-154)
      - Education--General: Federal Impact Legislation (Folder 155)
    - Education--Special: Vocational (Folder 156)
    - Education--Special: Vocational Rehabilitation (Barden-LaFollette Act) (Box 99, Folder 157)
    - Library Demonstration Bill (Folder 158)
    - Labor Relations: Taft-Hartley (Folder 159-162)
    - Labor Standards: Minimum Wage (Folder 163-166)
    - Labor Standards: Minimum Wage (Box 100, Folder 167-170)
    - Overtime Pay (Folder 171)
    - Labor: Legislation (Folder 172-174)
  - 82nd Congress 1951-1952
    - Education & Labor Comm.: General Papers (Folder 175)
    - Personnel (Box 101, Folder 176)
    - Subcommittee on Federal Aid to Education: (Folder 177)
      - Bailey Bill
      - Defense Housing (Folder 178)
      - General (Folder 179-181)
      - Impacted Areas (P.L. 874 & 815) (Folder 182-183)
    - Impacted Areas (Box 102, Folder 184)
    - Subcommittee on Federal Activities in Education (Folder 185)
    - Library Services (Folder 186-188)
    - Education--special:
      - Nursing (Folder 189)
      - School Health & Safety (Folder 190)
      - Scholarship Bill (Folder 191)
      - Vocational (Folder 192)
      - Blind Aid Bills (Folder 193)
      - Handicap Bills (Folder 194)
      - Handicap Bill (Box 103, Folder 195)
      - Vocational Rehabilitation (Folder 196)
    - Education: Legislation (Folder 197-198)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Defense Production: Wage Scale, Savannah River Project (Folder 199)
    - Labor--Wage Stabilization Board: Lucas Amendment (Folder 200)
    - Labor--Wage Stabilization Board:; Frank Slay (Folder 201)
    - Labor--Wage Stabilization Board: Steel Strike (Folder 202)
    - Labor--Wage Stabilization Board: General (Folder 203)
    - Labor--Wage Stabilization Board: General (Box 104, Folder 204-209)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Relations: Taft-Hartley (Box 105, Folder 210)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Relations: Industry-Wide Bargaining (Box 105, Folder 211)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Relations: Industry-Wide Bargaining (notebook) (Folder 212)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Relations: Paducah, Ky (Folder 213)
    - Labor Standards: Child Labor (H.R. 1271) (Folder 214-216)
    - Labor Standards: Walsh-Healy (Box 106, Folder 217)
    - Subcommittee on Coal Mine Safety (Folder 218-219)
    - Labor: Legislation (Folder 220-222)
  - 83rd Congress 1953-1954
    - Education & Labor Comm.: General Papers (Folder 223)
    - Education & Labor Comm.:Personnel (Folder 224)
    - Subcommittee on Investigation of Federal Educational Activities (Folder 225)
    - Special Subcommittee on Federal Aid to School Construction (Folder 226)
    - Special Subcommittee on Federal Aid to School Construction (Box 107, Folder 227-228)
    - Education--General: Emergency School Construction (Folder 229)
    - Education--General: Federal Impact (Folder 230)
    - Education--General: Hull Amendment (Oil Revenues) (Folder 231)
    - Education--Special: Randolph-Shepherd Bill (Blind) (Folder 232)
    - Education--Special: Handicapped (Folder 233)
    - Education--Special: Barden-LaFollette Act (Vocational Rehabilitation) (Folder 234)
    - Education--Special: Barden-LaFollette Act (Box 108, Folder 235)
    - Education--Special: Vocational Education (Folder 236-239)
    - Education: Legislation (Folder 240-242)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Smith Bill (H.R 3999) (Box 109, Folder 243)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Industry-Wide Bargaining (Folder 244)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Textile Industry (Folder 245)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee:; Murray-Dingell-Rhodes (Folder 246)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee:; International Typographical Union (notebook) (Folder 247)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Taft-Hartley (Folder 248-249)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Taft-Hartley, 1953 (Box 110, Folder 250-255)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Taft-Hartley, 1953-1954 (Box 111, Folder 256-261)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Taft-Hartley, 1954 (Box 112, Folder 262-267)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Taft-Hartley (Box 113, Folder 268-269)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Taft-Hartley (notebook) (Folder 270)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: NLRB (Folder 271-273)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee:; NLRB (Box 114, Folder 274-275)
    - Labor Relations Subcommittee: Railroad Closed Shop (PL 914) (Folder 276)
    - Labor Standards:; Davis Bacon (Folder 277)
    - Labor Standards: Minimum Wage (Folder 278)
    - Labor Standards: Fair Labor Standards Act (Folder 279)
    - Labor: Legislation (Folder 280-282)
    - Labor: Legislation (Box 135, Folder 283-286)
  - 84th Congress 1955-1956
    - Education & Labor Comm.: General Papers (Folder 287-289)
    - Education & Labor Comm.: Personnel (Box 116, Folder 290)
    - Subcommittee on Civilian Awards (Folder 291)
    - Education--General: Federal Aid (Folder 292-298)
    - Education--General: Federal Aid (Box 117, Folder 299-300)
    - Education--General: White House Conference (Folder 301)
    - Subcommittee to Amend P.L. 815-874: Impact Legislation (Folder 302)
    - Subcommittee to Amend P.L. 815-874: Quantico Schools (Folder 303)
    - Subcommittee to Amend P.L. 815-874: On-Base Schools (Folder 304)
    - Subcommittee to Amend P.L. 815-874: Indian Reservation Schools (Folder 305)
    - Subcom. on Federal Aid for Library Service (Box 118, Folder 306-308)
    - Subcommittee on Fine Arts (Folder 309)
    - Subcommittee on Aid to the Blind (Folder 310)
    - Education--Special: Retarded Children (Folder 311)
    - Education--Special: Juvenile Delinquency (Folder 312)
    - Education--Special: Vocational Rehabilitation (Folder 313)
    - Education--Special: Vocational Education (Folder 314)
    - Education--Special: Scholarships in Sciences (Folder 315)
    - Education: Legislation (Folder 316-317)
    - Subcommittee on Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 119, Folder 318-322)
    - Subcommittee on Fair Labor Standards Act: Windsor Cotton Company (Folder 323)
    - Subcommittee to Extend Minimum Wage to American Samoa, Guam, etc. (Folder 324)
    - Subcommittee to Extend Minimum Wage to American Samoa, Guam, etc. (Box 120, Folder 325-326)
    - Labor Standards: Davis Bacon Act (Folder 327)
    - Labor Relations: Taft-Hartley (Folder 328)
    - Labor Relations: Lundy Packing Company (Folder 329)
    - Labor Relations: Labor Unions (Folder 330)
    - Labor Relations: Railway Labor Act (Folder 331)
    - Labor Relations: Right to Work (Folder 332)
    - Labor Relations: Strikes (Box 121, Folder 333)
    - Labor Relations: Racketeering (Box 121, Folder 334)
    - Labor Relations: NLRB (Folder 335-336)
    - Subcommittee to Investigate Welfare and Pensions (Folder 337)
    - Subcommittee on Longshoremen's & Harbor Workers' Compensation Act (Folder 338)
    - Subcommittee on Mine Safety (Folder 339)
    - Employment Compensation (Folder 340)
    - Labor: Legislation (Folder 341-343)
  - 85th Congress 1957-1958
    - Education & Labor Committee: General Papers (Box 122, Folder 344-346)
    - Education & Labor Committee: Personnel (Folder 347)
    - Education & Labor Committee: Department Reports (Folder 348)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: General Papers (Folder 349)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Educational Recommendations and Scholarship Programs (Folder 350)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Educational Recommendations (Box 123, Folder 351)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Aid to School Construction (Folder 352-356)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Aid to School Construction (Box 124, Folder 357-363)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Aid to School Construction (Box 125, Folder 364-369)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Impact (Folder 370)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Impact (Box 126, Folder 371-373)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: General Papers (Folder 374)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Federal Advisory Council on the Arts (Folder 375)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Audiovisual Instruction (T11) (Folder 376)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Audiovisual Instruction (film) (Folder 377)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education:; Howard University (Box 127, Folder 378)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Blind Legislation (Folder 379-380)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Deaf Legislation (Folder 381)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Mentally Retarded Children (Folder 382)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Federal Agency for Handicapped (Folder 383)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Juvenile Delinquency (Folder 384)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Vocational Rehab. (Folder 385)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Library Services (Folder 386)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Vocational Education (Box 127, Folder 387)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Federal Grants (Education Beyond High School) (Folder 388)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Quattlebaum Report (Educational Needs and Military Manpower Policy) (Folder 389)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Barden Statements on Education as the Foundation For National Defense (Folder 390)
    - Education--Special: National Defense Education Act (Box 128, Folder 391-398)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Standards: General Papers (Folder 399)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Standards: Western Electric Wage Rates (Folder 400)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Standards: Supreme Court Labor Decisions (Folder 401)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Standards: Discrimination in Employment (Folder 402)
    - Subcommittee on Labor Standards: Minimum Wage Extension (Box 129, Folder 403-408)
    - Subcommittee on Safety and Compensation: General Papers (Folder 409)
    - Subcommittee on Safety and Compensation: The Aged (Folder 410)
    - Subcommittee on Safety and Compensation: Federal Employee's Compensation Act (Folder 411)
    - Subcommittee on Safety and Compensation: Longshoremen and Harbor Workers (Folder 412)
    - Subcommittee on Safety and Compensation: Mine Safety (Folder 413)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: General (Folder 414)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Petrillo-Interlochen Dispute (Box 130, Folder 415)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Taft-Hartley (Folder 416-417)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Racketeering (Folder 418)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Kennedy-Ives (Special) (Folder 419)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Kennedy-Ives (Folder 420-422)
    - Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Kennedy-Ives (Box 131, Folder 423-429)
    - Full Committee, Welfare and Pension Funds: Special (Box 132, Folder 430-433)
    - Full Committee, Welfare and Pension Funds:; J. P. Mitchell (Folder 434)
    - Full Committee, Welfare and Pension Funds: Bills introduced (Folder 435)
    - Full Committee, Welfare and Pension Funds: S. 2888 (Folder 436)
    - Full Committee, Welfare and Pension Funds: S. 2888 (Box 133, Folder 437-463)
    - Full Committee, Davis Bacon Act (Box 134, Folder 444)
    - Labor Legislation (Box 134, Folder 445-446)
  - 86th Congress 1959-1960
    - Education & Labor Committee: General Papers (Box 134, Folder 447)
    - Education & Labor Committee: Members (Folder 448)
    - Education & Labor Committee: Personnel (Folder 449)
    - Education & Labor Committee: Department Reports (Folder 450)
    - Subcom. on General Education: General Papers (Folder 451)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Aid, General (Box 135, Folder 452-454)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Federal Aid (School Construction) (Folder 455-457)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Impacted Areas (Folder 458)
    - Subcommittee on General Education: Impacted Areas (Civil Rights Act) (Folder 459)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: General Papers (Folder 460)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education:; Howard University (Box 136, Folder 461)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Fine Arts (Folder 462)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: the Blind (Folder 463)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: the Deaf (Folder 464)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Special Education and Rehabilitation Act (Folder 465-467)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Juvenile Delinquency (Folder 468)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Library Services (Folder 469)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education:; NDEA Loyalty Oath (Folder 470)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education:; NDEA (Box 137, Folder 471-475)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Obscene Literature (Folder 476)
    - Subcommittee on Special Education: Vocational Education (Folder 477)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Labor Reform (General) (Folder 478)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Labor Reform (Box 138, Folder 479-481)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Labor Issues Special (Folder 482)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: LIMB (Folder 483)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Airplane Strikes (Folder 484)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Newspaper Strikes (Folder 485)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Steel Strike (Folder 486)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Strikebreakers (Folder 487)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Secondary Boycott & Blackmail Picketing Examples (Box 139, Folder 488)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: No-Man's Land problem (Folder 489)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Textile Workers Union of America (Folder 490)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Garment Workers (Folder 491)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; International Association of Machinists (Box 139, Folder 492)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Structural Steel Fabricating Industry (Folder 493)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Teamsters, Union & Unloading Receipts (Folder 494-495)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Labor Union Releases (Folder 496)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Labor Reform (Outside summaries) (Folder 497)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; Sno-White Restaurant (Folder 498)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; National Association of Manufacturers (Folder 499)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Migratory Workers (Folder 500)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Small Business Association (Folder 501)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; James B. Carey (Folder 502)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; George Meaney (Folder 503)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; AFL-CIO Building and Construction, Fifth Annual Legislative Conference (loose folder) (Folder 504)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; AFL-CIO Building and Construction, Sixth Annual Conference (loose folder) (Folder 505)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; AFL-CIO (Folder 506)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations:; AFL-CIO (Box 140, Folder 507)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Internal Union Matters (Folder 508)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Testimony before subcommittee (Folder 509)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Labor Bill of Rights (Special, H. R. 4473) (Folder 510-514)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Labor Bill of Rights (General) (Folder 515)
    - Joint Subcom, on Labor Management Relations: Labor Bill of Rights (General, H. R. 4473) (Box 141, Folder 516-521)
    - Joint Subcom, on Labor-Management Relations: Labor Bill of Rights (General) (Box 142, Folder 522-527)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Labor (Box 143, Folder 528-529)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Labor Reform Debate Material (Folder 530-534)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: McLellan Labor Bill (Folder 535)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Kennedy-Erwin Bill (S. 1555) (Folder 536)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Kennedy-Erwin Bill (Box 144, Folder 537-540)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor Management Relations: Roosevelt Bill (Folder 541)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin Labor Bill (Box 144, Folder 542-543)
    - Joint Sitcom. on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 145, Folder 544-550)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 146, Folder 551-557)
    - Joint Subcom. on Labor-Management. Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 147, Folder 558-563)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 148, Folder 564-568)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 149, Folder 569-574)
    - Joint Subcom. on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 150, Folder 575-580)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum--Griffin (Box 151, Folder 581-586)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 152, Folder 587-592)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 153, Folder 593-599)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 154, Folder 600-605)
    - Joint Subcommittee on Labor-Management Relations: Landrum-Griffin (Box 155, Folder 606-611)